/* jshint esversion: 6 */
/* jshint -W033 */

// Questions - Debut

export const debutQuestions = [
    {
    "question": "And I was right there beside him all summer long",
    "answers": ["Picture to Burn", "Tim McGraw", "Cold As You", "Should Have Said No"],
    "correct": 1
    },

    {
    "question": "So watch me strike a match on all my wasted time",
    "answers": ["Picture to Burn", "Stay Beautiful", "Mary's Song (Oh My My My)", "Our Song"],
    "correct": 0
    },

    {
    "question": "The only thing that keeps me wishing on a wishing star",
    "answers": ["A Perfectly Good Heart", "Our Song", "Teardrops on My Guitar", "Should Have Said No"],
    "correct": 2
    },

        {
    "question": "I'm just walking, trying to see through the rain coming down",
    "answers": ["Place in this World", "Stay Beautiful", "Cold As You", "Picture to Burn"],
    "correct": 0
    },

    {
    "question": "Every smile you fake is so condescending, counting all the scars you made",
    "answers": ["Tim McGraw", "Invisible", "A Perfectly Good Heart", "Cold As You"],
    "correct": 3
    },

    {
    "question": "I know I didn't read between the lines",
    "answers": ["Stay Beautiful", "The Outside", "Mary's Song (Oh My My My)", "Tim McGraw"],
    "correct": 1
    },

    {
    "question": "But you don't tell anyone that you might not be the golden one",
    "answers": ["Our Song", "A Perfectly Good Heart", "Tied Together with a Smile", "Picture to Burn"],
    "correct": 2
    },

    {
    "question": "It's hard to make a conversation, when he's taking my breath away",
    "answers": ["Stay Beautiful", "Our Song", "The Outside", "Mary's Song (Oh My My My)"],
    "correct": 0
    },
    
    {
    "question": "You say that the past is the past",
    "answers": ["A Perfectly Good Heart", "Tim McGraw", "Tied Together with a Smile", "Should Have Said No"],
    "correct": 3
    },

    {
    "question": "Take me back to the house in the backyard tree",
    "answers": ["Should Have Said No", "Mary's Song (Oh My My My)", "The Outside", "Tim McGraw"],
    "correct": 1
    },

    {
    "question": "I've heard every album, listened to the radio",
    "answers": ["Our Song", "Picture to Burn", "Teardrops on My Guitar", "A Perfectly Good Heart"],
    "correct": 0
    },

    {
    "question": "And I don't try to hide my tears, my secrets or my deepest fears",
    "answers": ["Tim McGraw", "I'm Only Me When I'm With You", "The Outside", "Cold As You"],
    "correct": 1
    },

    {
    "question": "There's a fire inside of you that can't help but shine through",
    "answers": ["Picture to Burn", "Tied Together with a Smile", "Invisible", "Should Have Said No"],
    "correct": 2
    },

    {
    "question": "Why would you wanna make the very first scar",
    "answers": ["Our Song", "Tim McGraw", "Stay Beautiful", "A Perfectly Good Heart"],
    "correct": 3
    },

    {
    "question": "I hate that stupid old pickup truck you never let me drive",
    "answers": ["Picture to Burn", "Should Have Said No", "Mary's Song (Oh My My My)", "Invisible"],
    "correct": 0
    },

    {
    "question": "The water's high, you're jumping into it",
    "answers": ["Tim McGraw", "Tied Together with a Smile", "Cold As You", "Teardrops on My Guitar"],
    "correct": 1
    },

    {
    "question": "She said, I was seven and you were nine",
    "answers": ["Picture to Burn", "I'm Only Me When I'm With You", "Cold As You", "Mary's Song (Oh My My My)"],
    "correct": 3
    },

    {
    "question": "We could be a beautiful miracle, unbelievable",
    "answers": ["Our Song", "Should Have Said No", "Invisible", "Teardrops on My Guitar"],
    "correct": 2
    },

    {
    "question": "Maybe I should've seen the signs, should've read the writing on the wall",
    "answers": ["A Perfectly Good Heart", "Our Song", "The Outside", "Cold As You"],
    "correct": 0
    },

    {
    "question": "He said the way my blue eyes shined put those Georgia stars to shame that night",
    "answers": ["Invisible", "Tim McGraw", "Tied Together with a Smile", "Picture to Burn"],
    "correct": 1
    },

    {
    "question": "September saw a month of tears, and thankin' God that you weren't here",
    "answers": ["Our Song", "Invisible", "Tim McGraw", "Stay Beautiful"],
    "correct": 2
    },

    {
    "question": "You need one chance, it was a moment of weakness",
    "answers": ["Tied Together with a Smile", "Picture to Burn", "Cold as You", "Should Have Said No"],
    "correct": 3
    },

    {
    "question": "I was walkin' up the front porch steps after everything that day",
    "answers": ["Invisible", "Our Song", "Stay Beautiful", "Tim McGraw"],
    "correct": 1
    },

    {
    "question": "Well, you drive me crazy half the time",
    "answers": ["Cold as You", "Stay Beautiful", "I'm Only Me when I'm with You", "Invisible"],
    "correct": 2
    },

    {
    "question": "But your eyes still shined like pretty lights",
    "answers": ["Picture to Burn", "Mary's Song (Oh My My My)", "Teardrops on my Guitar", "Stay Beautiful"],
    "correct": 1
    },
];